JEREMY THIBEAU

22 Amroth Avenue, Toronto ON M4C 4H2 Phone: (506) 961-8852

Email: <u>thibeau.jeremy@gmail.com</u> Github: <u>github.com/jeremythibeau</u>

PROFILE

Innovative thinker with a focus on problem solving and multi-tasking. Experience with client service in the financial industry, programming in multiple languages, and a background in teaching and mathematics. Adaptable, resourceful, and willing to take on challenges.

EDUCATION

| George Brown College | 2020 | Computer Programmer Analyst Diploma |
|-----------------------|--------------|--|
| St. Thomas University | 2014 2013 | Bachelor of Education Bachelor of Arts, Major in Math, Minor in English & Psychology |
| Riverview High School | 2009 | New Brunswick Secondary School Diploma |

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & SOFTWARE EXPERIENCE

- . C#
- Python
- SQL
- Java
- HTML
- JavaScript
- PHP
- MongoDB

- GitHub
- Eclipse
- Angular
- Visual Studio
- ASP.NET
- Android Studio
- Node.js

WORK EXPERIENCE

| Tangerine | 2015 - 2015 2015 2014 - 2015 | Client Solutions Lead Mortgage Specialist Savings Specialist Savings Associate |
|----------------|---------------------------------------|---|
| Brunswick News | 2010 - 2014 | Customer Service Representative |

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

| Bliss Carmen Middle School | 2014 | Teaching Internship, Science and Social Studies |
|----------------------------|------|---|
| Moncton High School | 2013 | Teaching Internship, Mathematics |

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

| George Brown College | 2018 - 2020 | Dean's List (6 semesters) |
|----------------------|-------------|--|
| Tangerine | _ | Top Mortgage Specialist, Quality Top Savings Associate, Quality |

REFERENCES

References are available upon request.